

Skills

- Javascript, Typescript
- React.JS, Redux
- HTML
- CSS, SCSS
- Webpack, Parcel
- Git
- Figma
- Responsive/adaptative web design
- Unit tests (Jest, React Testing Library)

Languages

English – Intermediate (B1)

Polish - Beginner (A1)

Russian - Native

Soft skills

- Attentive to details
- Easy learning
- Responsible

Hobbies

Assembling PCs, looking for bugs in apps & games, cheating in PC games, reading sci-fi.

Travel, ride a motorcycle, off-road driving.

Anton Borkovskij

Phone: <u>+375 29 1279490</u> Email: <u>member@tut.by</u>

GitHub: github.com/g5-freemen

LinkedIn: anton-borkovskij-097995200

Telegram: g5 freemen

Profile

I worked as a mining master, but computers and IT have always been a hobby of mine since childhood. I learned how to build and configure computers, write programs and small games, look for bugs in applications, games and even BIOS.

I've completely changed my field of work and am currently working as a Front-end developer.

Education

2000 - 2005

Belarusian National Technical University Faculty of Natural Resources & Ecology Specialization: Mining Engineer Bachelor of Engineering Science

Courses

August 2021 - September 2021

The Rolling Scopes School, React

Creating apps using functional component & hooks. React-Router.

February 2021 – August 2021

The Rolling Scopes School, **JavaScript/Front-End** Creating pages/apps using HTML, CSS, JS, Typescript, Webpack, Figma. Code review.

September 2020 - April 2021

Coding School TeachMeSkills, Front End Developer Creating web applications using HTML, CSS, SCSS, JS, TS, React, Redux, Figma, Webpack or Parcel. Responsive/adaptive web design. Writing unit tests.

Work experience

September 2021 – now

Fresh Lime Soft LLC, Front-end (React) developer

May 2012 - September 2021

JSC "Nerudprom", senior mining master

February 2010 - May 2012

JSC "Nerudprom", chief of precinct

September 2005 – February 2010

JSC "Nerudprom", mining master

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Project Name	<u>JoVE</u>
Duration	5 Months (June 2022 - October 2022)
Project description	JoVE is the world-leading producer and provider of science videos with the mission to improve scientific research and education. Millions of scientists, educators and students at thousands of universities, colleges, hospitals and bio pharmaceutical companies worldwide use JoVE for their research, teaching and learning.
Project role	Front-end developer
Project team size	10+ team members
Tasks performed	 Create pages Bugfixes App caching & optimization
Environment	 React.js Redux TypeScript React-Query Axios Chakra UI Formik + Yup
Project Name	Raise the Grade
Project Name Duration	Raise the Grade 8 + 2 Months (October 2021 - May 2022, November 2022 – December 2022)
Duration Project	8 + 2 Months (October 2021 - May 2022, November 2022 – December 2022) Web application for registering for food safety course. This application included different admin and client functionality. Admins were able to create classes and register new Clients, and Clients in their turn register their students for the course. After passing exam, students were given certificates and
Duration Project description	8 + 2 Months (October 2021 - May 2022, November 2022 – December 2022) Web application for registering for food safety course. This application included different admin and client functionality. Admins were able to create classes and register new Clients, and Clients in their turn register their students for the course. After passing exam, students were given certificates and Client could download it from the system.
Duration Project description Project role	8 + 2 Months (October 2021 - May 2022, November 2022 – December 2022) Web application for registering for food safety course. This application included different admin and client functionality. Admins were able to create classes and register new Clients, and Clients in their turn register their students for the course. After passing exam, students were given certificates and Client could download it from the system. Front-end developer

Project Name	Anytime Soccer
Duration	1 Month (January 2023)
Project description	Web application for registering for food safety course. This application included different admin and client functionality. Admins were able to create classes and register new Clients, and Clients in their turn register their students for the course. After passing exam, students were given certificates and Client could download it from the system.
Project role	Front-end developer
Project team size	3 team members
Tasks performed	BugfixesAdding new featuresOptimization
Environment	 React.js Redux Redux-Thunk Formik + Yup SASS